yellowbook360.com 2010-12-25

# Yellowbook Privacy Policy at Yellowbook.com

Yellowbook recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our policies and practices relating to the collection, use and storage of information provided to us by users of the Yellowbook.com website (the "Site").

## What information does Yellowbook collect?

Yellowbook collects personal information that you knowingly provide to us. For example, Yellowbook may ask you to provide your contact information (such as name, address, email address, telephone number and account password) if you inquire about advertising with us, sign up for a free listing in a Yellowbook directory, register to post ratings and reviews, or otherwise contact us through the Site.

In addition, as you use the Site, our web servers automatically retrieve certain information about your browsing activity such as IP address, domain name, browser agent and user access information such as number and duration of Site visits and pages visited.

## How does Yellowbook use the information collected?

When you provide personal information for a specific purpose (for example, registering to use a feature on the Site), we generally use it for that purpose.

We may use personal information you provide to: communicate with you and to otherwise serve you. For example, we may use your name, address and email address to send you emails to (a) contact you regarding advertising services you have requested, (b) provide information about Yellowbook and our affiliates, including marketing information about products and services and newsletters, (c) conduct online surveys, (d) contact you in connection with user reviews, (e) publish your name, address, and phone number in our directories (unless you have asked us not to publish this information), and (f) otherwise communicate with you.

We may retain and use emails or other communications you send to Yellowbook in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

In addition, Yellowbook may use personal information you provide in combination with the information Yellowbook automatically collects through the Site to protect our property or other rights (for example, to enforce any policies or contractual provisions regarding copyright, use of the "ratings and reviews" feature or the "save and send" feature of the Site).

## Information Sharing

Yellowbook will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below. We may share personal information with others in the following limited circumstances:

  * With other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our Site.
  * With other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users.

We may share aggregated, non-personal information about Site usage to improve on the quality of services we offer. We may also provide such aggregated data to our customers, business partners, or third-party vendors, in which case specific users will be anonymous. In addition, we may share your ratings and reviews with other businesses with which we partner.

## What about cookies?

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on particular sites, thus enabling website owners to provide more useful features for their users. The use of cookies is an industry standard. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our Site if you do so.

## Third Party Advertisers

We use third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on this Site, other websites and other forms of media. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Updating Personal Information; Opting Out

You may review and request changes to the personal information you have provided to us by viewing and updating your account profile through the myYellowbook feature of the Site.

You may request not to receive (i.e., "opt-out" of receiving) promotional email messages from us, by unchecking the checkbox beside the "I wish to receive updates and information from Yellowbook" line on the myYellowbook account registration page. Please note that we reserve the right to send certain types of email messages that are not subject to opt-out to users who have opted out of receiving email messages.

## Links to Third Party Sites

Links to external websites owned and operated by third parties ("Third Party Sites") may be presented in a format that enables Yellowbook to keep track of whether these links have been followed. This information is used in aggregated form to improve our services to Yellowbook users and advertisers.

Yellowbook does not exercise control over Third Party Sites to which you may link from this Site. These Third Party Sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, or collect personal information from you. If you decide to access any such Third Party Site, you do so at your own risk, and we refer you to the privacy policy of such Third Party Site.

## Security

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to personal information to Yellowbook employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, up to and including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Yellowbook.com is not designed to attract children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through Yellowbook.com and not to information collected offline.

## Conditions of Use

For information about the terms and conditions governing your use of our Site, please review the Yellowbook.com Conditions of Use at [http://www.yellowbook.com/conditionsofuse](http://www.yellowbook.com/conditionsofuse/).

## Privacy Policy Updates

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, store or share your personal information, we will prominently post a notice of the changes on Yellowbook.com.
